that was the first meditation that's
part of the long room where was reached
the part where we talk about protection
and how to get protection you can call
it protection you can call it shelter
you can call it refuge but how do you
get protection when you have problems or
in your life so a big part of that
protection is to recognize that there is
a person who loves you millions of times
stronger than you love yourself they are
ready to protect you and I just want you
to come and ask okay so that was the
first meditation there is a being many
Buddhist they know what you're thinking
they watch you all day
they're probably wincing all day but
they care about us and and you have to
understand the dad there they are
waiting and they like to protect you
they want to help you okay you just have
to learn how to reach them okay so that
was the first meditation and that's the
first review from what we did in
Thailand